const quizDataFromFile = [
  {
    "question": "die Ansage, -n",
    "correct": "announcement",
    "choices": [
      "announcement",
      "hall",
      "November",
      "statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Anschluss",
    "correct": "connection",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "board (dining)",
      "time",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Anschluss",
    "correct": "connection",
    "choices": [
      "weather",
      "friend",
      "brother",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Antwort, -en",
    "correct": "answer",
    "choices": [
      "answer",
      "eye",
      "passport",
      "post office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Anzeige, -n",
    "correct": "advert",
    "choices": [
      "advert",
      "son",
      "jacket",
      "train station"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Apartment, -s",
    "correct": "apartment",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "househusband",
      "mouth",
      "apartment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Apfel, -Ä",
    "correct": "apple",
    "choices": [
      "bus",
      "hunger",
      "apple",
      "Monday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Appetit",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "potato",
      "fridge",
      "minute",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Arbeit, -en",
    "correct": "work",
    "choices": [
      "work",
      "(female) partner",
      "film",
      "identity card"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Arbeitsplatz, -ä, e",
    "correct": "workplace",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "workplace",
      "view",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Arm, -e",
    "correct": "arm",
    "choices": [
      "(public transport) stop",
      "board (dining)",
      "east",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Arzt, -Ä, e",
    "correct": "doctor",
    "choices": [
      "information",
      "morning",
      "doctor",
      "sister"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Aufgabe, -n",
    "correct": "task",
    "choices": [
      "potato",
      "task",
      "customer",
      "CD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Aufzug, -ü, e",
    "correct": "lift",
    "choices": [
      "lift",
      "connection",
      "shop",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Auge, -n",
    "correct": "eye",
    "choices": [
      "double room",
      "foot",
      "sun",
      "eye"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ausflug",
    "correct": "excursion",
    "choices": [
      "regards",
      "occupation",
      "excursion",
      "customs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ausgang",
    "correct": "exit",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "husband",
      "exit",
      "hotel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Auskunft, -ü, e",
    "correct": "information/details",
    "choices": [
      "luggage",
      "mistake",
      "information/details",
      "problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ausland",
    "correct": "abroad/overseas",
    "choices": [
      "cafe",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "pear",
      "bank holiday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ausländer, -",
    "correct": "foreigner",
    "choices": [
      "appointment",
      "foreigner",
      "class",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Aussage, -n",
    "correct": "statement",
    "choices": [
      "statement",
      "hall",
      "Ms",
      "disco"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ausweis",
    "correct": "identity card",
    "choices": [
      "identity card",
      "bread",
      "landlord",
      "weekend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Auto, -s",
    "correct": "car",
    "choices": [
      "passport",
      "car",
      "home",
      "end of work/home time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Autobahn, -en",
    "correct": "motorway",
    "choices": [
      "single room",
      "driver",
      "HGV",
      "motorway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Automat",
    "correct": "machine",
    "choices": [
      "name",
      "glasses",
      "police",
      "machine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Baby, -s",
    "correct": "baby",
    "choices": [
      "salt",
      "baby",
      "February",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bäckerei",
    "correct": "bakery",
    "choices": [
      "(male) partner",
      "square",
      "bakery",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Bad",
    "correct": "bathroom",
    "choices": [
      "balcony",
      "bathroom",
      "breakfast",
      "weekend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bahn",
    "correct": "train",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "name",
      "room",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bahn",
    "correct": "train",
    "choices": [
      "recipient",
      "salesperson",
      "examination",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bahnhof",
    "correct": "train station",
    "choices": [
      "tour guide",
      "toilet",
      "weight",
      "train station"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bahnsteig",
    "correct": "platform",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "summer",
      "platform",
      "tram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Balkon",
    "correct": "balcony",
    "choices": [
      "balcony",
      "cafe",
      "number",
      "signature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Banane, -n",
    "correct": "banana",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "tram",
      "banana",
      "travel guide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bank",
    "correct": "bank",
    "choices": [
      "bank",
      "brother",
      "July",
      "solution"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bank",
    "correct": "bench",
    "choices": [
      "information",
      "sentence",
      "doctor",
      "bench"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bauch",
    "correct": "stomach",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "sea",
      "stomach",
      "landlord"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Baum, -ä, e",
    "correct": "tree",
    "choices": [
      "end of work/home time",
      "cake",
      "information/details",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Beamte, -n",
    "correct": "official",
    "choices": [
      "housewife",
      "official",
      "card",
      "film"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Bein, -e",
    "correct": "leg",
    "choices": [
      "club",
      "leg",
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Beispiel, -e",
    "correct": "example",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "example",
      "company",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Beruf, -e",
    "correct": "profession",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "shop",
      "bench",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Beruf, -e",
    "correct": "occupation",
    "choices": [
      "occupation",
      "map / plan",
      "sun",
      "ball-point pen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Bett, -en",
    "correct": "bed",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "grandmother",
      "conversation/talk/call",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Bier",
    "correct": "beer",
    "choices": [
      "key",
      "(female) partner",
      "beer",
      "picture"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Bild, -er",
    "correct": "picture",
    "choices": [
      "entry",
      "picture",
      "answer",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Birne, -n",
    "correct": "pear",
    "choices": [
      "(female) partner",
      "solution",
      "pear",
      "afternoon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Bitte, -n",
    "correct": "request",
    "choices": [
      "bicycle",
      "grandfather",
      "colour",
      "request"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bleistift, -e",
    "correct": "pencil",
    "choices": [
      "group",
      "colour",
      "motorway",
      "pencil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Blick",
    "correct": "view",
    "choices": [
      "view",
      "degree course",
      "February",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Blume, -n",
    "correct": "flower",
    "choices": [
      "women",
      "flower",
      "dictionary",
      "doctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bogen",
    "correct": "sheet",
    "choices": [
      "head",
      "excursion",
      "examination",
      "sheet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Brief, -e",
    "correct": "letter",
    "choices": [
      "end of work/home time",
      "letter",
      "lake",
      "mother"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Briefmarke, -n",
    "correct": "(postage) stamp",
    "choices": [
      "August",
      "boss",
      "sun",
      "(postage) stamp"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Brot, -e",
    "correct": "bread",
    "choices": [
      "location / place",
      "telephone",
      "(flight) departure",
      "bread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Brot, -e",
    "correct": "bread roll",
    "choices": [
      "restaurant",
      "bread roll",
      "example",
      "doctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Brötchen, –",
    "correct": "bread roll",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "bread roll",
      "weather",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bruder, -ü",
    "correct": "brother",
    "choices": [
      "telephone",
      "thanks",
      "examination",
      "brother"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Buch, -ü, er",
    "correct": "book",
    "choices": [
      "first name",
      "topic",
      "group",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wörterbuch, -ü, er",
    "correct": "dictionary",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "examination",
      "…",
      "dictionary"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Buchstabe, -n",
    "correct": "letter (character)",
    "choices": [
      "letter (character)",
      "foot",
      "kindergarten",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Bus, -se",
    "correct": "bus",
    "choices": [
      "bus",
      "number",
      "price",
      "airport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Butter",
    "correct": "butter",
    "choices": [
      "oil",
      "boss",
      "butter",
      "doctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Café, -s",
    "correct": "cafe",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "cafe",
      "seat",
      "airport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die CD, -s",
    "correct": "CD",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "rent",
      "grandparents",
      "CD"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Chef",
    "correct": "boss",
    "choices": [
      "request",
      "boss",
      "passport",
      "journey / trip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Computer, –",
    "correct": "computer",
    "choices": [
      "room",
      "computer",
      "thanks",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Dame, -n",
    "correct": "lady",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "computer",
      "train",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Dame, -n",
    "correct": "lady",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "single room",
      "midday",
      "hand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Dank",
    "correct": "thanks",
    "choices": [
      "thanks",
      "potato",
      "bag",
      "attention"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Dank",
    "correct": "thanks",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "thanks",
      "fruit",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Datum",
    "correct": "date",
    "choices": [
      "housewife",
      "degree course",
      "date",
      "pencil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Disco",
    "correct": "disco",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "disco",
      "school",
      "street"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Doktor",
    "correct": "doctor",
    "choices": [
      "Thursday",
      "telephone",
      "doctor",
      "counter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Doppelzimmer",
    "correct": "double room",
    "choices": [
      "double room",
      "commuter train",
      "school",
      "tram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Dorf, -ö, er",
    "correct": "village",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "village",
      "midday",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Drucker, –",
    "correct": "printer",
    "choices": [
      "area code",
      "letter (character)",
      "July",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Durchsage, -n",
    "correct": "announcement",
    "choices": [
      "announcement",
      "mistake",
      "…",
      "attention"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Durst",
    "correct": "thirst",
    "choices": [
      "adult",
      "thirst",
      "banana",
      "post office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Dusche",
    "correct": "shower",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "grandfather",
      "Friday",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Ecke, -n",
    "correct": "corner",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "car",
      "moment",
      "wind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Ehefrau, -en/",
    "correct": "wife",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "luck",
      "shoe",
      "day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ehemann, ä, er",
    "correct": "husband",
    "choices": [
      "husband",
      "June",
      "information",
      "bench"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ei, -er",
    "correct": "egg",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "bus",
      "wind",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Eingang",
    "correct": "entrance",
    "choices": [
      "entrance",
      "papers",
      "question",
      "travel guide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Einladung",
    "correct": "invitation",
    "choices": [
      "boss",
      "machine",
      "invitation",
      "bakery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Eintritt",
    "correct": "entry",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "entry",
      "date",
      "shop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Einzelzimmer",
    "correct": "single room",
    "choices": [
      "grandfather",
      "telephone",
      "single room",
      "signature"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Eltern (pl.)",
    "correct": "parents",
    "choices": [
      "identity card",
      "parents",
      "room",
      "tram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die E-Mail, -s",
    "correct": "email",
    "choices": [
      "song",
      "baby",
      "shop",
      "email"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Empfänger, –",
    "correct": "recipient",
    "choices": [
      "recipient",
      "thanks",
      "lift",
      "time"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ende",
    "correct": "end",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "part",
      "question",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ende",
    "correct": "end",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "end",
      "course",
      "football"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Entschuldigung",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "kindergarten",
      "price",
      "mouth",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ergebnis, -se",
    "correct": "result",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "summer",
      "student",
      "result"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Erwachsene, -n",
    "correct": "adult",
    "choices": [
      "adult",
      "computer",
      "coffee",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Essen",
    "correct": "food",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "wine",
      "film",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Fahrer",
    "correct": "driver",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "driver",
      "birth year",
      "post / mail"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Fahrkarte, -n",
    "correct": "(transport) ticket",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "(transport) ticket",
      "bag",
      "house / building"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Fahrrad, -ä, er",
    "correct": "bicycle",
    "choices": [
      "bicycle",
      "bread roll",
      "group",
      "statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Familie, -n",
    "correct": "family",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "colleague",
      "family",
      "degree course"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Familienname",
    "correct": "surname",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "student",
      "company",
      "surname"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Familienstand",
    "correct": "family/marital status",
    "choices": [
      "foreigner",
      "salesperson",
      "family/marital status",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Farbe, -n",
    "correct": "colour",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "beer",
      "colour",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Fax, -e",
    "correct": "fax",
    "choices": [
      "fax",
      "task",
      "swimming pool",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Feierabend",
    "correct": "end of work/home time",
    "choices": [
      "end of work/home time",
      "entry",
      "present",
      "wind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Feiertag",
    "correct": "bank holiday",
    "choices": [
      "night",
      "home",
      "bank holiday",
      "paper"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Fehler, –",
    "correct": "mistake",
    "choices": [
      "Thursday",
      "end",
      "mistake",
      "aeroplane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Feuer",
    "correct": "fire / lighter",
    "choices": [
      "party",
      "bottle",
      "fire / lighter",
      "post office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Fieber",
    "correct": "fever",
    "choices": [
      "birthday",
      "…",
      "dog",
      "fever"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Film, -e",
    "correct": "film",
    "choices": [
      "bread roll",
      "film",
      "name",
      "work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Firma",
    "correct": "company",
    "choices": [
      "club",
      "rice",
      "company",
      "family/marital status"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Fisch, -e",
    "correct": "fish",
    "choices": [
      "fish",
      "child",
      "birthday",
      "hotel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Flasche, -n",
    "correct": "bottle",
    "choices": [
      "butter",
      "corner",
      "bottle",
      "middle"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Fleisch",
    "correct": "meat",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "meat",
      "family/marital status",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Abflug",
    "correct": "(flight) departure",
    "choices": [
      "(flight) departure",
      "moment",
      "part",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Flughafen",
    "correct": "airport",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "location / place",
      "glasses",
      "airport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Flugzeug",
    "correct": "aeroplane",
    "choices": [
      "aeroplane",
      "machine",
      "May",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Formular, -e",
    "correct": "form",
    "choices": [
      "form",
      "company",
      "family/marital status",
      "tour guide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Foto, -s",
    "correct": "photograph",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "Mister",
      "minute",
      "motorway"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Frage, -n",
    "correct": "question",
    "choices": [
      "spring",
      "people",
      "wind",
      "question"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Frau",
    "correct": "Ms",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "Ms",
      "sights/attractions",
      "money"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Frau",
    "correct": "woman",
    "choices": [
      "cigarette",
      "present",
      "repair",
      "woman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Frauen",
    "correct": "women",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "women",
      "hour",
      "train station"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Freizeit",
    "correct": "free time",
    "choices": [
      "free time",
      "foot",
      "bed",
      "double room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Freund, -e",
    "correct": "friend",
    "choices": [
      "adult",
      "friend",
      "free time",
      "life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Freundin",
    "correct": "friend / girlfriend",
    "choices": [
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "pub",
      "signature",
      "statement"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Frühstück",
    "correct": "breakfast",
    "choices": [
      "first name",
      "announcement",
      "grandfather",
      "breakfast"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Führung",
    "correct": "tour",
    "choices": [
      "August",
      "identity card",
      "tour",
      "regards"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Fuß, -ü, e",
    "correct": "foot",
    "choices": [
      "foot",
      "bank holiday",
      "name",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Fußball",
    "correct": "football",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "football",
      "tree",
      "glass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Garten",
    "correct": "garden",
    "choices": [
      "bank",
      "garden",
      "Monday",
      "winter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Gast, -ä, e",
    "correct": "guest",
    "choices": [
      "guest",
      "August",
      "square",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Geburtsjahr",
    "correct": "birth year",
    "choices": [
      "October",
      "(public transport) stop",
      "birth year",
      "bread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Geburtsort",
    "correct": "birthplace",
    "choices": [
      "girl",
      "seat",
      "stairs",
      "birthplace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Geburtstag",
    "correct": "birthday",
    "choices": [
      "(female) partner",
      "birthday",
      "attention",
      "weekend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Geld",
    "correct": "money",
    "choices": [
      "pupil",
      "money",
      "film",
      "weight"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Gemüse",
    "correct": "vegetables",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "foot",
      "west",
      "vegetables"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Gepäck",
    "correct": "luggage",
    "choices": [
      "luggage",
      "January",
      "lake",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Geschäft, -e",
    "correct": "shop",
    "choices": [
      "view",
      "pear",
      "shop",
      "May"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Geschenk, -e",
    "correct": "present",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "Saturday",
      "tea",
      "present"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Geschwister (pl.)",
    "correct": "sibling",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "commuter train",
      "connection",
      "sibling"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Gespräch, -e",
    "correct": "conversation/talk/call",
    "choices": [
      "aeroplane",
      "luck",
      "help",
      "conversation/talk/call"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Getränk, -e",
    "correct": "drink",
    "choices": [
      "drink",
      "lake",
      "text",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Gewicht",
    "correct": "weight",
    "choices": [
      "guest",
      "weight",
      "hobby",
      "bank holiday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Glas, -ä, er",
    "correct": "glass",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "week",
      "dictionary",
      "glass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Glas, -ä, er",
    "correct": "glasses",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "view",
      "glasses",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Gleis, -e",
    "correct": "platform",
    "choices": [
      "platform",
      "arm",
      "information/details",
      "town / city"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Glück",
    "correct": "luck",
    "choices": [
      "kitchen",
      "luck",
      "surname",
      "test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Glückwunsch",
    "correct": "congratulations",
    "choices": [
      "bathroom",
      "luggage",
      "oil",
      "congratulations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Größe",
    "correct": "size",
    "choices": [
      "size",
      "dog",
      "group",
      "bread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Großeltern (pl.)",
    "correct": "grandparents",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "wind",
      "grandparents",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Großmutter",
    "correct": "grandmother",
    "choices": [
      "grandmother",
      "evening",
      "butter",
      "group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Großvater",
    "correct": "grandfather",
    "choices": [
      "shoe",
      "grandfather",
      "sibling",
      "information point"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Gruppe, -n",
    "correct": "group",
    "choices": [
      "account",
      "…",
      "group",
      "sheet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Gruß, -ü, e",
    "correct": "regards",
    "choices": [
      "regards",
      "song",
      "motorway",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Gruß, -ü, e",
    "correct": "regards",
    "choices": [
      "regards",
      "papers",
      "son",
      "stomach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Haar, -e",
    "correct": "hair",
    "choices": [
      "hair",
      "class",
      "July",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Hähnchen, -",
    "correct": "chicken",
    "choices": [
      "topic",
      "work",
      "chicken",
      "board (dining)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Halbpension",
    "correct": "board (dining)",
    "choices": [
      "mobile telephone",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "board (dining)",
      "till"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Halle",
    "correct": "hall",
    "choices": [
      "hall",
      "July",
      "moment",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Haltestelle",
    "correct": "(public transport) stop",
    "choices": [
      "(public transport) stop",
      "chicken",
      "juice",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hand, -ä, e",
    "correct": "hand",
    "choices": [
      "entry",
      "doctor",
      "tram",
      "hand"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Handy, -s",
    "correct": "mobile telephone",
    "choices": [
      "pupil",
      "mobile telephone",
      "signature",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Haus, -ä, er",
    "correct": "house / building",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "name",
      "signature",
      "house / building"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Haus, -ä, er",
    "correct": "home",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "home",
      "chicken",
      "sun"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Haus, -ä, er",
    "correct": "home",
    "choices": [
      "home",
      "bread",
      "fruit",
      "south"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hausaufgabe,-n",
    "correct": "homework",
    "choices": [
      "Thursday",
      "women",
      "house / building",
      "homework"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hausfrau, -en/",
    "correct": "housewife",
    "choices": [
      "housewife",
      "course",
      "letter (character)",
      "relative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Hausmann",
    "correct": "househusband",
    "choices": [
      "girl",
      "househusband",
      "example",
      "moment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Heimat",
    "correct": "home",
    "choices": [
      "location / place",
      "home",
      "(male) partner",
      "school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Herd",
    "correct": "stove",
    "choices": [
      "stove",
      "commuter train",
      "mouth",
      "congratulations"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Herr, -en",
    "correct": "Mister",
    "choices": [
      "letter",
      "rain",
      "Mister",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hilfe",
    "correct": "help",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "text",
      "woman",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hilfe",
    "correct": "help",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "north",
      "family",
      "group"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Hobby, -s",
    "correct": "hobby",
    "choices": [
      "counter",
      "paper",
      "Monday",
      "hobby"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Hochzeit",
    "correct": "marriage",
    "choices": [
      "cigarette",
      "marriage",
      "room",
      "day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Hotel, -s",
    "correct": "hotel",
    "choices": [
      "view",
      "hunger",
      "grandparents",
      "hotel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Hund, -e",
    "correct": "dog",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "dog",
      "winter",
      "information point"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Hunger",
    "correct": "hunger",
    "choices": [
      "balcony",
      "table",
      "hunger",
      "bag"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Information, -en",
    "correct": "information point",
    "choices": [
      "mouth",
      "meat",
      "school",
      "information point"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Information, -en",
    "correct": "information",
    "choices": [
      "information",
      "bank holiday",
      "mouth",
      "conversation/talk/call"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Internet",
    "correct": "internet",
    "choices": [
      "internet",
      "moment",
      "Monday",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Jacke, -n",
    "correct": "jacket",
    "choices": [
      "rice",
      "jacket",
      "life",
      "bread"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Job, -s",
    "correct": "job",
    "choices": [
      "announcement",
      "job",
      "single room",
      "August"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Jugendliche, -n",
    "correct": "youth/young person",
    "choices": [
      "regards",
      "table",
      "thanks",
      "youth/young person"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Junge, -n",
    "correct": "boy",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "bus",
      "result",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kaffee",
    "correct": "coffee",
    "choices": [
      "boss",
      "house / building",
      "customer",
      "coffee"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Karte, -n",
    "correct": "card",
    "choices": [
      "workplace",
      "card",
      "chicken",
      "glasses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Karte, -n",
    "correct": "card",
    "choices": [
      "card",
      "post office",
      "repair",
      "October"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Karte, -n",
    "correct": "menu",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "topic",
      "sun",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Kartoffel, -n",
    "correct": "potato",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "potato",
      "youth/young person",
      "test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Kasse",
    "correct": "till",
    "choices": [
      "entry",
      "connection",
      "CD",
      "till"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Kind, -er",
    "correct": "child",
    "choices": [
      "child",
      "end of work/home time",
      "film",
      "birthplace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kindergarten",
    "correct": "kindergarten",
    "choices": [
      "single room",
      "postcode",
      "kindergarten",
      "birthplace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Kino, -s",
    "correct": "cinema",
    "choices": [
      "cinema",
      "car",
      "flower",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kiosk",
    "correct": "kiosk",
    "choices": [
      "people",
      "kiosk",
      "moment",
      "son"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Klasse",
    "correct": "class",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "number",
      "letter",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Klasse",
    "correct": "class",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "practice",
      "grandfather",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Kleidung",
    "correct": "clothes",
    "choices": [
      "househusband",
      "clothes",
      "room",
      "banana"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Koffer, –",
    "correct": "suitcase",
    "choices": [
      "occupation",
      "tomato",
      "suitcase",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kollege, -n",
    "correct": "colleague",
    "choices": [
      "fax",
      "bus",
      "colleague",
      "card"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Konto",
    "correct": "account",
    "choices": [
      "account",
      "thanks",
      "result",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kopf",
    "correct": "head",
    "choices": [
      "official",
      "wind",
      "mouth",
      "head"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Küche",
    "correct": "kitchen",
    "choices": [
      "kitchen",
      "wine",
      "luggage",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kuchen",
    "correct": "cake",
    "choices": [
      "seat",
      "lake",
      "jacket",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kugelschreiber",
    "correct": "ball-point pen",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "grandmother",
      "swimming pool",
      "ball-point pen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kühlschrank",
    "correct": "fridge",
    "choices": [
      "restaurant",
      "fridge",
      "machine",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kunde, -n",
    "correct": "customer",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "double room",
      "bank holiday",
      "customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Kurs, -e",
    "correct": "course",
    "choices": [
      "boss",
      "course",
      "…",
      "Friday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Laden, -ä",
    "correct": "shop",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "weekday",
      "January",
      "shop"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Land, -ä, er",
    "correct": "country",
    "choices": [
      "girl",
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "country",
      "stomach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Leben",
    "correct": "life",
    "choices": [
      "card",
      "moment",
      "life",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Lebensmittel (pl.)",
    "correct": "food",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "May",
      "week",
      "Tuesday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Lehrer, –",
    "correct": "teacher",
    "choices": [
      "grandfather",
      "shop",
      "middle",
      "teacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Leute (pl.)",
    "correct": "people",
    "choices": [
      "view",
      "people",
      "driver",
      "board (dining)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Licht",
    "correct": "light",
    "choices": [
      "coffee",
      "April",
      "homework",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Lied, -er",
    "correct": "song",
    "choices": [
      "song",
      "help",
      "sign",
      "problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Lkw, -s",
    "correct": "HGV",
    "choices": [
      "announcement",
      "HGV",
      "daughter",
      "name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Lokal",
    "correct": "pub",
    "choices": [
      "street",
      "night",
      "morning",
      "pub"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Lösung, -en",
    "correct": "solution",
    "choices": [
      "solution",
      "sport",
      "rain",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Mädchen, –",
    "correct": "girl",
    "choices": [
      "girl",
      "fridge",
      "tomato",
      "information/details"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mann, -ä, er",
    "correct": "man / husband",
    "choices": [
      "man / husband",
      "task",
      "butter",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Maschine, -n",
    "correct": "machine",
    "choices": [
      "letter (character)",
      "second",
      "machine",
      "July"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Meer",
    "correct": "sea",
    "choices": [
      "sea",
      "evening",
      "weather",
      "teacher"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mensch, -en",
    "correct": "people",
    "choices": [
      "ticket",
      "people",
      "sights/attractions",
      "glass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Miete",
    "correct": "rent",
    "choices": [
      "people",
      "rent",
      "…",
      "invitation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Milch",
    "correct": "milk",
    "choices": [
      "clothes",
      "platform",
      "doctor",
      "milk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Mitte",
    "correct": "middle",
    "choices": [
      "home",
      "daughter",
      "middle",
      "email"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Möbel (pl.)",
    "correct": "furniture",
    "choices": [
      "furniture",
      "rent",
      "birth year",
      "stairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Moment",
    "correct": "moment",
    "choices": [
      "letter",
      "picture",
      "moment",
      "October"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Moment",
    "correct": "moment",
    "choices": [
      "adult",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "moment",
      "suitcase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mund",
    "correct": "mouth",
    "choices": [
      "workplace",
      "mouth",
      "…",
      "sights/attractions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Mutter, -ü",
    "correct": "mother",
    "choices": [
      "official",
      "mother",
      "meat",
      "till"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Name, -n",
    "correct": "name",
    "choices": [
      "glasses",
      "potato",
      "name",
      "woman"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Name, -n",
    "correct": "name",
    "choices": [
      "postcode",
      "map / plan",
      "wife",
      "name"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Nummer, -n",
    "correct": "number",
    "choices": [
      "househusband",
      "number",
      "hour",
      "October"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Nummer, -n",
    "correct": "number",
    "choices": [
      "househusband",
      "form",
      "number",
      "September"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Obst",
    "correct": "fruit",
    "choices": [
      "telephone",
      "car",
      "fruit",
      "course"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Öl",
    "correct": "oil",
    "choices": [
      "recipient",
      "oil",
      "brochure",
      "apple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Oma, -s",
    "correct": "grandmother",
    "choices": [
      "grandmother",
      "example",
      "flat",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Opa, -s",
    "correct": "grandfather",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "sentence",
      "grandfather",
      "midday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Ordnung",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "Saturday",
      "…",
      "fever"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Ort, -e",
    "correct": "location / place",
    "choices": [
      "location / place",
      "course",
      "flat",
      "problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Papier",
    "correct": "paper",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "cinema",
      "paper",
      "customs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Papiere (pl.)",
    "correct": "papers",
    "choices": [
      "song",
      "May",
      "papers",
      "relative"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Partner, -/",
    "correct": "(male) partner",
    "choices": [
      "people",
      "(male) partner",
      "name",
      "sign"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Partnerin, -nen",
    "correct": "(female) partner",
    "choices": [
      "rice",
      "(female) partner",
      "son",
      "letter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Party",
    "correct": "party",
    "choices": [
      "information",
      "car",
      "party",
      "apple"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Pass, -ä, e",
    "correct": "passport",
    "choices": [
      "passport",
      "number",
      "January",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Pause, -n",
    "correct": "break",
    "choices": [
      "map / plan",
      "friend",
      "middle",
      "break"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Plan, -ä, e",
    "correct": "map / plan",
    "choices": [
      "map / plan",
      "pear",
      "sibling",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Platz, -ä, e",
    "correct": "seat",
    "choices": [
      "appointment",
      "seat",
      "commuter train",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Platz, -ä, e",
    "correct": "seat",
    "choices": [
      "seat",
      "room",
      "train",
      "foreigner"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Platz, -ä, e",
    "correct": "square",
    "choices": [
      "area code",
      "grandmother",
      "square",
      "street"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Polizei",
    "correct": "police",
    "choices": [
      "thanks",
      "police",
      "text",
      "floor (of a building)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Pommes frites (pl.)",
    "correct": "chips",
    "choices": [
      "chips",
      "name",
      "tree",
      "light"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Post",
    "correct": "post office",
    "choices": [
      "man / husband",
      "travel guide",
      "airport",
      "post office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Post",
    "correct": "post / mail",
    "choices": [
      "year",
      "post / mail",
      "(male) partner",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Postleitzahl",
    "correct": "postcode",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "postcode",
      "grandmother",
      "table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Praktikum",
    "correct": "internship",
    "choices": [
      "counter",
      "room",
      "internship",
      "eye"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Praxis",
    "correct": "practice",
    "choices": [
      "counter",
      "practice",
      "number",
      "milk"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Preis, -e",
    "correct": "price",
    "choices": [
      "bread roll",
      "price",
      "congratulations",
      "February"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Problem, -e",
    "correct": "problem",
    "choices": [
      "counter",
      "food",
      "problem",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Prospekt, -e",
    "correct": "brochure",
    "choices": [
      "chips",
      "east",
      "brochure",
      "invitation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Prüfung",
    "correct": "examination",
    "choices": [
      "aeroplane",
      "north",
      "examination",
      "meat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Raum, -ä, e",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "street",
      "statement",
      "grandfather",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Rechnung, -en",
    "correct": "bill",
    "choices": [
      "bill",
      "mother",
      "house / building",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Regen",
    "correct": "rain",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "bathroom",
      "rain",
      "till"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Reis",
    "correct": "rice",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "letter (character)",
      "rice",
      "email"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Reise",
    "correct": "journey / trip",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "foot",
      "Wednesday",
      "journey / trip"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Reisebüro, -s",
    "correct": "travel agency",
    "choices": [
      "sheet",
      "telephone",
      "Tuesday",
      "travel agency"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Reiseführer",
    "correct": "travel guide",
    "choices": [
      "advert",
      "kindergarten",
      "rent",
      "travel guide"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Reiseführer",
    "correct": "tour guide",
    "choices": [
      "tour guide",
      "student",
      "pupil",
      "email"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Reparatur",
    "correct": "repair",
    "choices": [
      "man / husband",
      "garden",
      "…",
      "repair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Restaurant, -s",
    "correct": "restaurant",
    "choices": [
      "restaurant",
      "foot",
      "account",
      "cake"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Rezeption",
    "correct": "reception",
    "choices": [
      "connection",
      "thanks",
      "break",
      "reception"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Saft",
    "correct": "juice",
    "choices": [
      "appointment",
      "swimming pool",
      "house / building",
      "juice"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Salat",
    "correct": "salad",
    "choices": [
      "salad",
      "brochure",
      "winter",
      "connection"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Salz",
    "correct": "salt",
    "choices": [
      "invitation",
      "salt",
      "thanks",
      "work"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Satz, -ä, e",
    "correct": "sentence",
    "choices": [
      "youth/young person",
      "sentence",
      "middle",
      "email"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die S-Bahn",
    "correct": "commuter train",
    "choices": [
      "child",
      "commuter train",
      "doctor",
      "arm"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schalter",
    "correct": "counter",
    "choices": [
      "counter",
      "bank",
      "garden",
      "morning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Schild, -er",
    "correct": "sign",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "sign",
      "week",
      "request"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schinken, –",
    "correct": "ham",
    "choices": [
      "ham",
      "Sunday",
      "hair",
      "vegetables"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schluss",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "weekday",
      "parents",
      "…",
      "taxi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schluss",
    "correct": "end",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "water",
      "CD",
      "glass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schlüssel, –",
    "correct": "key",
    "choices": [
      "key",
      "recipient",
      "home",
      "kitchen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schrank, -ä, e",
    "correct": "cupboard",
    "choices": [
      "end of work/home time",
      "cupboard",
      "travel guide",
      "customs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schuh, -e",
    "correct": "shoe",
    "choices": [
      "east",
      "name",
      "shoe",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Schule",
    "correct": "school",
    "choices": [
      "life",
      "grandmother",
      "man / husband",
      "school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Schule",
    "correct": "school",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "board (dining)",
      "family/marital status",
      "school"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Schüler, –",
    "correct": "pupil",
    "choices": [
      "dog",
      "present",
      "April",
      "pupil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Schwester, -n",
    "correct": "sister",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "ticket",
      "sister",
      "brother"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Schwimmbad",
    "correct": "swimming pool",
    "choices": [
      "aeroplane",
      "swimming pool",
      "moment",
      "life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der See",
    "correct": "lake",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "topic",
      "lake",
      "life"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Sehenswürdigkeit, -en",
    "correct": "sights/attractions",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "morning",
      "glasses",
      "sights/attractions"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Sofa",
    "correct": "sofa",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "salesperson",
      "September",
      "sofa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Sohn, -ö, e",
    "correct": "son",
    "choices": [
      "foot",
      "kindergarten",
      "task",
      "son"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Sonne",
    "correct": "sun",
    "choices": [
      "sun",
      "Tuesday",
      "room",
      "stomach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Speisekarte",
    "correct": "menu",
    "choices": [
      "drink",
      "fax",
      "flat",
      "menu"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Sport",
    "correct": "sport",
    "choices": [
      "form",
      "sport",
      "commuter train",
      "board (dining)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Sprache, -n",
    "correct": "language",
    "choices": [
      "language",
      "fax",
      "chips",
      "tree"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Stadt, -ä, e",
    "correct": "town / city",
    "choices": [
      "kiosk",
      "Mister",
      "moment",
      "town / city"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Stelle, -n",
    "correct": "job / position",
    "choices": [
      "internet",
      "job / position",
      "entry",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Stock",
    "correct": "floor (of a building)",
    "choices": [
      "picture",
      "company",
      "suitcase",
      "floor (of a building)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Straße, -n",
    "correct": "street",
    "choices": [
      "street",
      "school",
      "conversation/talk/call",
      "club"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Straßenbahn",
    "correct": "tram",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "mother",
      "…",
      "tram"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Studium",
    "correct": "degree course",
    "choices": [
      "degree course",
      "train station",
      "train",
      "egg"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Student, -en",
    "correct": "student",
    "choices": [
      "butter",
      "househusband",
      "student",
      "hunger"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Stunde, -n",
    "correct": "hour",
    "choices": [
      "August",
      "…",
      "hour",
      "morning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Tasche, -n",
    "correct": "bag",
    "choices": [
      "guest",
      "end of work/home time",
      "bag",
      "morning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Taxi, -s",
    "correct": "taxi",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "adult",
      "June",
      "taxi"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Tee",
    "correct": "tea",
    "choices": [
      "tea",
      "car",
      "till",
      "glass"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Teil, -e",
    "correct": "part",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "part",
      "glasses",
      "result"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Telefon",
    "correct": "telephone",
    "choices": [
      "telephone",
      "wind",
      "November",
      "profession"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Termin, -e",
    "correct": "appointment",
    "choices": [
      "postcode",
      "appointment",
      "colleague",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Test",
    "correct": "test",
    "choices": [
      "photograph",
      "Mister",
      "apartment",
      "test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Text, -e",
    "correct": "text",
    "choices": [
      "(public transport) stop",
      "potato",
      "text",
      "class"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Thema",
    "correct": "topic",
    "choices": [
      "topic",
      "luggage",
      "salesperson",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Ticket, -s",
    "correct": "ticket",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "ticket",
      "dog",
      "week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Tisch, -e",
    "correct": "table",
    "choices": [
      "luggage",
      "signature",
      "east",
      "table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Tochter, -ö",
    "correct": "daughter",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "cigarette",
      "daughter",
      "pencil"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Toilette, -en",
    "correct": "toilet",
    "choices": [
      "end",
      "view",
      "surname",
      "toilet"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Tomate, -n",
    "correct": "tomato",
    "choices": [
      "women",
      "daughter",
      "tomato",
      "sofa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Treppe, -n",
    "correct": "stairs",
    "choices": [
      "answer",
      "sentence",
      "youth/young person",
      "stairs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Uhr",
    "correct": "o'clock / am / pm",
    "choices": [
      "airport",
      "shop",
      "o'clock / am / pm",
      "suitcase"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Unterricht",
    "correct": "class",
    "choices": [
      "class",
      "statement",
      "househusband",
      "card"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Unterschrift",
    "correct": "signature",
    "choices": [
      "money",
      "signature",
      "tree",
      "day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Urlaub",
    "correct": "holiday",
    "choices": [
      "holiday",
      "luck",
      "moment",
      "daughter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Vater, -ä",
    "correct": "father",
    "choices": [
      "bathroom",
      "father",
      "house / building",
      "printer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Verein",
    "correct": "club",
    "choices": [
      "club",
      "fax",
      "pupil",
      "book"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Verkäufer, –",
    "correct": "salesperson",
    "choices": [
      "aeroplane",
      "salesperson",
      "chips",
      "winter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Vermieter",
    "correct": "landlord",
    "choices": [
      "February",
      "break",
      "landlord",
      "head"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Verwandte, -n",
    "correct": "relative",
    "choices": [
      "milk",
      "relative",
      "February",
      "test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Vorname, -n",
    "correct": "first name",
    "choices": [
      "first name",
      "foreigner",
      "second",
      "moment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Vorsicht",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "square",
      "…"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Vorsicht",
    "correct": "attention",
    "choices": [
      "brother",
      "email",
      "attention",
      "customs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Vorwahl",
    "correct": "area code",
    "choices": [
      "area code",
      "disco",
      "pear",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wasser",
    "correct": "water",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "water",
      "examination",
      "glasses"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Wein",
    "correct": "wine",
    "choices": [
      "double room",
      "wine",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "July"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Welt",
    "correct": "world",
    "choices": [
      "world",
      "job / position",
      "first name",
      "parents"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wetter",
    "correct": "weather",
    "choices": [
      "pear",
      "mouth",
      "…",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wiederhören",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "(male) partner",
      "night",
      "…",
      "ball-point pen"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wiedersehen",
    "correct": "…",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "clothes",
      "…",
      "post office"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Wind",
    "correct": "wind",
    "choices": [
      "balcony",
      "first name",
      "north",
      "wind"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Wohnung, -en",
    "correct": "flat",
    "choices": [
      "home",
      "daughter",
      "…",
      "flat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wort, -ö, er/-e",
    "correct": "word",
    "choices": [
      "word",
      "boss",
      "kindergarten",
      "shower"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Zeit",
    "correct": "time",
    "choices": [
      "water",
      "village",
      "time",
      "internship"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Zeitung, -en",
    "correct": "newspaper",
    "choices": [
      "newspaper",
      "passport",
      "balcony",
      "airport"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Zigarette, -n",
    "correct": "cigarette",
    "choices": [
      "cigarette",
      "leg",
      "square",
      "repair"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Zimmer, –",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "help",
      "…",
      "adult",
      "room"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Zimmer, –",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "bank",
      "(male) partner",
      "room",
      "hotel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Zimmer, –",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "workplace",
      "room",
      "invitation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Zimmer, –",
    "correct": "room",
    "choices": [
      "entry",
      "bill",
      "room",
      "conversation/talk/call"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Zoll",
    "correct": "customs",
    "choices": [
      "platform",
      "bread",
      "tomato",
      "customs"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Zug, -ü, e",
    "correct": "train",
    "choices": [
      "street",
      "corner",
      "east",
      "train"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Sekunde, -n",
    "correct": "second",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "second",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "job"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Minute, -n",
    "correct": "minute",
    "choices": [
      "appointment",
      "picture",
      "minute",
      "customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Stunde, -n",
    "correct": "hour",
    "choices": [
      "internet",
      "Sunday",
      "moment",
      "hour"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Tag, -e",
    "correct": "day",
    "choices": [
      "hair",
      "end",
      "Mister",
      "day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Woche, -e",
    "correct": "week",
    "choices": [
      "lady",
      "machine",
      "salesperson",
      "week"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Jahr, -e",
    "correct": "year",
    "choices": [
      "year",
      "swimming pool",
      "family/marital status",
      "homework"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Wochentag, -e",
    "correct": "weekday",
    "choices": [
      "weekday",
      "end",
      "moment",
      "morning"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Sonntag",
    "correct": "Sunday",
    "choices": [
      "Sunday",
      "water",
      "husband",
      "customer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Montag",
    "correct": "Monday",
    "choices": [
      "girl",
      "language",
      "work",
      "Monday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Dienstag",
    "correct": "Tuesday",
    "choices": [
      "colleague",
      "example",
      "Tuesday",
      "tomato"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mittwoch",
    "correct": "Wednesday",
    "choices": [
      "luggage",
      "price",
      "Wednesday",
      "sofa"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Donnerstag",
    "correct": "Thursday",
    "choices": [
      "Thursday",
      "salad",
      "Monday",
      "doctor"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Freitag",
    "correct": "Friday",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "Thursday",
      "student",
      "Friday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Samstag/Sonnabend",
    "correct": "Saturday",
    "choices": [
      "…",
      "Saturday",
      "birth year",
      "apartment"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "das Wochenende",
    "correct": "weekend",
    "choices": [
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "Mister",
      "o'clock / am / pm",
      "weekend"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Tag",
    "correct": "day",
    "choices": [
      "wife",
      "class",
      "meat",
      "day"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Morgen",
    "correct": "morning",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "cupboard",
      "table",
      "location / place"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Vormittag,-e",
    "correct": "morning",
    "choices": [
      "morning",
      "commuter train",
      "pear",
      "table"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mittag",
    "correct": "midday",
    "choices": [
      "room",
      "midday",
      "…",
      "father"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Nachmittag,-e",
    "correct": "afternoon",
    "choices": [
      "ham",
      "October",
      "wine",
      "afternoon"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Abend,-e",
    "correct": "evening",
    "choices": [
      "dictionary",
      "home",
      "evening",
      "hotel"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Nacht,¨-e",
    "correct": "night",
    "choices": [
      "stove",
      "food",
      "night",
      "problem"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Januar",
    "correct": "January",
    "choices": [
      "post / mail",
      "January",
      "task",
      "house / building"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Februar",
    "correct": "February",
    "choices": [
      "number",
      "break",
      "February",
      "bakery"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der März",
    "correct": "March",
    "choices": [
      "boy",
      "March",
      "question",
      "aeroplane"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der April",
    "correct": "April",
    "choices": [
      "kitchen",
      "April",
      "paper",
      "test"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Mai",
    "correct": "May",
    "choices": [
      "(transport) ticket",
      "lift",
      "May",
      "flat"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Juni",
    "correct": "June",
    "choices": [
      "food",
      "bicycle",
      "June",
      "head"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Juli",
    "correct": "July",
    "choices": [
      "conversation/talk/call",
      "tea",
      "sights/attractions",
      "July"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der August",
    "correct": "August",
    "choices": [
      "August",
      "January",
      "flower",
      "weather"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der September",
    "correct": "September",
    "choices": [
      "bed",
      "workplace",
      "part",
      "September"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Oktober",
    "correct": "October",
    "choices": [
      "afternoon",
      "entry",
      "result",
      "October"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der November",
    "correct": "November",
    "choices": [
      "friend / girlfriend",
      "card",
      "November",
      "wine"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Dezember",
    "correct": "December",
    "choices": [
      "hall",
      "platform",
      "December",
      "south"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Frühling/das Frühjahr",
    "correct": "spring",
    "choices": [
      "kiosk",
      "spring",
      "abroad/overseas",
      "bank holiday"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Sommer",
    "correct": "summer",
    "choices": [
      "postcode",
      "summer",
      "example",
      "stomach"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Herbst",
    "correct": "autumn",
    "choices": [
      "sport",
      "train",
      "colour",
      "autumn"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Winter",
    "correct": "winter",
    "choices": [
      "corner",
      "second",
      "pub",
      "winter"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Norden",
    "correct": "north",
    "choices": [
      "north",
      "home",
      "leg",
      "workplace"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Süden",
    "correct": "south",
    "choices": [
      "word",
      "grandfather",
      "minute",
      "south"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Westen",
    "correct": "west",
    "choices": [
      "topic",
      "wine",
      "village",
      "west"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "der Osten",
    "correct": "east",
    "choices": [
      "group",
      "east",
      "juice",
      "break"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "die Nummer, -n",
    "correct": "number",
    "choices": [
      "foreigner",
      "number",
      "film",
      "banana"
    ]
  }
];